This is draft season presented by
Moody's, a proud partner of the New York
Football Giants. I am John Schmilk,
joined as always by a fellow exhausted
friend and colleague, Tony Pauline from
Essentially Sports. Tony, uh, we are
recording this just to be perfectly
upfront with people. Um, about halfway
through round number six, maybe two 3/4
of the way through round number six. So,
if we miss some of your favorite uh,
seventh round draft picks when we go
through our team byte- draft review
here, I apologize in advance. But we
wanted to get this up as quickly as
possible for the folks. So, we're
recording it a little bit early.
>> Yeah. But by the time we're by the time
we're done with this podcast, all seven
rounds, you know, could be completed.
And I'll say this, credit to the league
because at least day one and day two,
they had good pace. I mean, the the the
draft really didn't lag as it had in the
past. And even day three is moving along
at a good pace.
>> Yes. Absolutely right. Our goal here,
folks, at the start is to get this all
done in one podcast. We'll see how it
goes. If we find it goes too long, maybe
we'll split it into two. We'll see. But
the goal right two checks for me. I'm
okay with that.
>> All right, let's try to knock this out.
We're going to go division by division
um and and see where people think about
um the NFL drafter. So, why don't we
start Tony um in the NFC East? We'll
start with the team that won that
division and we're have to navigate team
by team here as we go. So, bear with us
if we have to do some word salad to kind
of get team to team here. Uh but we're
going to start with the Philadelphia
Eagles since they won the NFC East last
year, Tony. And and so far as of this
recording, just four picks for them. Not
common for the Eagles. Usually they have
a bunch of picks in the mid- rounds.
They trade a couple fours to move up in
round one to draft Mai Lemon. They draft
Eli Sters in round number two. Markeel
Bell again looking ahead. Uh that's what
the Eagles do, right? They're looking
ahead. The AJ Brown trade round one wide
receiver. Looking ahead, Dallas Goddard
signed a one-year deal, right? He's
probably be gone after this year. as
your replacement, Markeel Bell. Oh, wait
a second. Lane Johnson, he might not be
back next year. Might retire. There's an
offensive tackle for you. And then
classic Eagles, they just draft another
quarterback. One of your favorites, Cole
Payton in round number five. Um, look,
again, not a ton of picks, but I think
the Eagles did pretty well. Got some
good players to help uh four offensive
players, which is something different
for them, too.
>> Stole lemon from the Pittsburgh
Steelers, who evidently wanted him. not,
you know, not the size of AJ Brown, but
really more refined coming into the
league as far as a compared to AJ Brown.
Uh, terrific route runner, catches the
ball well. You got to love his
competitive uh, attitude, wants that
football. Eli Ster, the type of tight
end that the Eagles have consistently
and historically had success with, that
move type of tight end that is a better
pass catcher than a than a blocker. So,
that was a terrific pick. Markeel Bell,
you know, it's interesting. They
selected Cameron Williams last year, if
you remember, a massive offensive
lineman. They come back with Markeel
Bell, who had a great season, left
tackle at Miami, projects to the right
side. Really, I I think an underrated
player that if he gets his weight down a
little bit and continues on this path,
has a future in the NFL. And Cole
Payton, I would have taken him late in
round three, early in round four. The
Eagles and Harry Roseman take him in
round five. I I mean, a lot of upside
there. And there's questions about
Jaylen Herz, Cole Payton, only a
one-year starter. We love them at the
Senior Bowl. They know how to develop
quarterbacks. You got Tanner McKe there.
You know, it gives them some options at
the position. All right, let's jump to
the Dallas Cowboys. I'll try to do this
in the order of the standings last year,
but I'll be honest with you, I'm pretty
tired. I might mess that up, but I'll do
my best. Uh Dallas Cowboys coming up
next year. Uh Caleb DS falls into the
laps of pick number 11. Tony, we talked
about this on our review show that we
thought that was a great fit for them if
you want to go back to the show uh
before this on your feeds from Thursday
night, Friday morning. Malachi Lawrence,
uh the edge, then Jan Barum in round
number three. Then three fourth round
picks. Again, they got in that trade
down from from pick 20 to 23. Uh Drew
Shelton out of Penn State, who we had
high hopes for before the year, didn't
necessarily develop, but certainly hits
a lot of buttons when it comes to
traits. Devin Moore has had some injury
issues. also a Tracy quarterback. And
then LT Overton, who I know people
thought of an edge before the year, but
I really think he's more of like a 34
defensive end and an interior player.
Big, long, powerful type of guy. A
>> lot of defense, which is what the
Cowboys needed. And I like what they
did. Obviously, you know, we've talked
about Caleb DS, one of the best players
in this draft. They get him at the 11
selection. I'm not sold on Malachi
Lawrence, but I like his upside. We
talked to him at the Shrine Bowl.
Wellspoken individual. He's just got to
develop his game. I love the pick of bar
of baram at the in the third round at
number 92. I think he's a great system
fit. He's more than an edge rusher. He's
a linebacker that can also play in
space. Drew Shelton has got great upside
as you said, didn't have a good season
and hurt his hamstring at the combine.
Really wasn't able to do much prior to
the draft. Some teams project him inside
the guarder center. We'll have to keep
an eye on that. Deon Moore is a guy
that's got great upside. He has terrific
size. He's got solid ball skills, better
facing the action. I think he may even
get some consideration at safety, but I
I think Deon Moore is a guy that makes
the active roster. And you basically
said it with LT Overton. I mean, he's an
explosive lineman that can play on the
outside, very likely on the inside, and
again fits that Dallas system. All
right, then let's go to the Washington
Commanders, Tony. Not a lot of picks
here uh because of various trades over
the course couple years for veterans.
There's a first, third, fifth, and
sixth. They have one more six and a
seventh coming down the pike here. Sunny
Styles at seven. You know, Dan Quinn
wanted the defensive leader. Got him.
Antonio Williams, nice slot receiver.
He'll he'll slide in there uh very well.
I think I think you love the value of
Joshua Joseph in round five. He's one of
your guys. And I love the value of Kron
Allen in round six. Look,
>> I think he's going to fight Rashad White
and and those guys that they have in
there, uh Nicholls and I think Jerome
Ford's there now, too. He'll fight for
playing time with those guys. kind of
there between the tackles running back.
>> Not a lot of picks, especially early
early on, but they made the most of
their selection. Sunonny Styles was the
guy that Dan Quinn wanted. I mean, he is
probably the best the purest offball
linebacker. And as somebody said to me,
you want to improve your defense, get a
fast mic. That's exactly what Sunny
Styles is. Antonio Williams, they needed
a receiver. Antonio Williams struggled
last year with hamstring issues. If
Antonio Williams can get back to where
he was in 2024 and take off from there,
at the very least, the Commanders have
wide receiver number three with return
skills. Joshua Joseph fits the edge
rushing need that they have. Fell into
the fifth round. There were some off
the- field concerns. There were size
speed issues, but if you watch the film,
he's a terrific pass rusher. And I'm
right there with you on Kron Allen. I
mean, the the commanders have gone
running back by committee last year.
that may start off like that, but Kron
Allen, don't be surprised if he grabs
hold of that starting job by the end of
the season.
>> Yeah, that would not shock me either.
I'm 100% with you. All right, uh let's
jump over now to the New York Giants.
Their their their draft day is done,
Tony. Uh we already talked about Alvaro
Reese and Francis Mau with five and 10
really good fits in the system. Um Bobby
Jameson, Travis, JC Davis, and Jack
Kelly, their three sixth round picks,
but let's focus first, Tony, on their
picks on day two. uh Colted Hood out of
Tennessee. They got him a pick 37 and
Malachi Fields at pick number 74.
Trading three picks to move into that
spot. Your thoughts on the Hood and
Fields additions in those spots?
>> Well, I think they wanted Kade McDonald,
but the Houston Texans jumped in front
of him in order to take Kade McDonald.
So, the Giants take Colton Hood. Fills a
need. Large quarterback has got a lot of
upside. Just needs to polish his game
and refine it. And if he does, I think
Hton Hood can become the quarterback
that the Giants hoped Deont uh Banks was
going to be who but never became. So, I
thought that was a sensational pick.
Very bold for the move from Malachi
Fields. But you know what? Once Malik
Neighbors gets healthy and is on the
field, Malachi Fields is the perfect
complimentary receiver to him. A big
body contested throw catch guy that can
go over the middle. Red zone threat.
Sneaky fast. He's much faster than the
46 he ran at the combine. But again, you
know, they needed a receiver and I think
this is a great compliment for Malik
Neighbors.
>> And then Bobby Jameson and Travis just a
widebody in the middle. JC Davis, I
think he's he's the guy that's going to
move into guard. Joe Shane and um John
Harour said as much. He's kind of a
guard, a swing guard, a tackle. And then
Jack Kelly, who I think is going to be a
core special team, linebacker who has
played edge and off ball out of BYU.
>> Jameson Jameson Travis more of a gap
occupier. I guess someone that they hope
if they don't sign somebody in free
agency can try and replace Dexter
Lawrence. He's not the playmaker of
Dexter Lawrence, but you want a guy to
occupy the middle of of the line and
take up blockers. He'll do that. I agree
with you about JC Davis. I think the
appeal to Harbaugh is he is he is really
a tough punch in the mouth, hit after
the whistle type of blocker. And Jack
Kelly's a serviceable linebacker, but as
you said, it's going to have to make
earn his wage on special teams. All
right, let's go to the Chicago Bears now
on top of the NFC North. It's it's weird
to say that, but they did uh they they
got all the way to the uh deep in the
playoffs here. Uh Dylan Theamman, we
talked about him. Really good pick at
25. Then Tony, I got to be honest with
you, the the next three picks I was
like, eh.
>> Logan Jones at center I thought in round
two for for a guy that's a little
undersized I thought was was a little
high. Sam Roush I thought was, you know,
I guess that's okay value at pick 69 at
tight end if you need a blocking tight
end there, but they already have two
really good tight ends there. So, I'm
not sure when he's going to get on the
field. Xavian Thomas, he's a fast wide
receiver, but he's, you know, really
small. The production's not really
there. But then I do like the day three
picks. I think Malik Muhammad round four
is a really good value as a good
quarterback. And I thought Keshan
Elliott as as kind of a run stuffing
linebacker in the middle of the field. I
thought that was pretty good value in
round five.
>> Damn, as we said, you know, really fits
that Chicago persona. A tough,
explosive, hard hitter. obviously
started his college career not too far
down the road at Purdue. I thought that
was an excellent pick. I agree with you
at Logan Jones. If you followed me at
Essentials Sports during the proday
month, I said that the Bears were going
to take a center somewhere on day two. I
thought it may have been Sam Heck. They
went with Logan Jones. You know, he's
got to get bigger. He's got to get
beefier. They have Garrett Bradberry
there who they they traded for. We'll
see. Maybe they develop Logan Jones uh
beneath him. I agree with you about Sam
Rush. They not they, you know, they took
Coloulston Lovelin with the 10th pick of
the draft. Why take another uh tight end
in the third round? Plus, I thought
there were better tight ends on the
board when they selected Rush. So, I
thought the Rush that So, that was a bit
of a reach. I like Xavian Thomas. Do I
like him in the third round? No, I had
him more as a fifth round selection, but
if you watch the film, he's a terrific
pass catcher. We saw him at the Shrine
Bowl and he was tough to stop. And oh,
by the way, he ran 428 at the combine.
So, I like this V. I also love the pick
of Malik Muhammad, a tall, rangy uh
corner with terrific ball skills who ran
much faster than expected at Proday. And
Elliot, like you said, he's going to be
a serviceable maybe nickel linebacker
that's going to have to play special
teams.
>> No question about it. All right, let's
jump over to the uh the Green Bay
Packers here. Tony did not have a first
round pick that was sent to Dallas in
the Micah Parsons trade. Uh Brandon Cis
in round number two. One of our
favorites, Chris Mlelen. I thought in
round three was a very nice pick. I
thought deny Dennis Sutton in round
number four was a very good value pick
from the Packers. Really three
aggressive physical players with the
first three picks. Jagger Burton, the
center out of Kentucky in round number
five. And then Demani Jackson, the
corner out of Alabama in the sixth.
>> CCI, I think, went where he should have
gone. People were talking about late
first. I mean, he's got a lot of upside,
but he needs to really polish his game.
Mlelen was one of my favorites. I know
they like Lee Hunter. He came off the
board before they were selecting in
round two. Men, I think, could be a
steal. He beat you with quickness,
explosion, power, and hustle. He's got
the entire package, and they need a nose
tackle. Dennis Danny Sutton, if they're
able to basically get him to play to his
level of ability on each and every down.
This was a steal in the fourth round.
Jacob Burton, he's a guy that his
testing numbers are very good. His
athletic testing numbers are terrific.
He doesn't play the way he tests. So, if
you're able to merge the two, you got a
real good starting uh interior offensive
lineman. And Demani Jackson is a very
athletic uh quarterback who showed a lot
of ability early in his Alabama career
yet never developed. So, if you're able
to develop either him or or Domani
Jackson, you have a guy that could be a
starting Nickelback on Sunday.
>> All right, let's jump over um to the
Minnesota Vikings here, Tony. Um, and
again, I think couple picks here that I
really like. Couple picks that I raised
my eyebrows at a little bit. Um, Caleb
Banks, uh, in the first round out of
Florida. We talked a lot about that. We
don't have to waste a ton of time there
because we talked about that on
Thursday's show. We both thought it was
very high. Big risk there. Uh, Jake
Gold, uh, the linebacker picked number
51. I thought they picked him over a
couple players that I like a little bit
better than him, but good player. Dom in
round three, I think is good value, but
so two defensive tackles for the
Vikings. Uh Caleb Tieran in round three,
the really tall offensive tackle. Uh
Jacobe Thomas, the safety out of Miami
in round three. I thought that was a
little bit rich for me. Um they want a
fullback. Max Bredesen. I will never be
upset with the team for picking a
fullback. I love fullbacks. Round five
out of Michigan. And then two picks I do
like. Charles Dennings out of Stephen F.
Austin. I interviewed him at the Senior
Bowl. Really good personality. Um
electric kid. And then Deon Claybourne
getting all the way to round six. Man,
you want a you want a a running back
that's going to bring some juice to get
De Man Claybourne around six. I think
that's pretty good value.
>> We talked about Caleb Banks as you
mentioned. I I thought Gay went exactly
where he was supposed to. I think he's a
a good fit for Minnesota. He's a smart
heady linebacker who will be able to
absorb that Brian Flores system. So, I I
like that pick. You know, I agree with
you. I mean, I like Dom Orange in the
third round. And you never know, Dom in
round three could turn out to be a
better pick than Caleb Banks in round
one. I I mean, because he fits that, you
know, nose tackle, uh, gap occupier
role, but he's and he's also relatively
athletic. Caleb Tieran was a guy who was
moving up draft boards, super athletic,
you know, he played left tackle at
Northwestern. I think he's more of a
right tackle, maybe guard, but he's got
some upside. Jacobe Thomas, terrific
player, but I think he was selected
really three to four rounds too early. I
like Bredesen, you know, a lead
fullback. Again, I thought it was a
little bit early for him. Charles
Demings is a guy that you just have to
develop. He's tall, he's fast, he's
explosive, he's flash ball skills, but a
small school guy that'll need some time.
The Mont Clairborn's got all got all the
tools to be a terrific situational
runner. Uh, dropped into the sixth round
because of off the- field issues,
character concerns. If you talk to him,
you would never know about it. Uh, but
he's got the ability to be a terrific
situational back.
Okay, let's go to the Detroit Lions, who
believe it or not, finished in last
place in the NFC North last year. Uh
Blake Miller, uh we both think will be a
solid tackle, but maybe a little bit
rich at 17. And then just a bunch of
like Lions picks, right? Derek Mo in
Michigan, not just that he's from
Michigan, but a super physical,
heavy-handed player. Jimmy Ralder, kind
of a bluecollar linebacker in round
number four. They did not have a third
round pick. Uh Keith Abney, uh the
quarterback at Arizona State, I thought
was really good value in round number
five. I thought he could have been a day
two selection. Then Kendrick Law, the
wide receiver out of Kentucky, and
Skyler Gil Howard, defensive tackle out
of Texas Tech.
>> Yeah, as you both said, I mean, Blake
Miller, in my opinion, was selected way
too early, but they need a tackle.
They're going to plug him in, I'm sure,
on the right side, move Penny SW to the
left side. Derek Moore, I love the
selection in the middle of round two.
You know, he's just a guy who you can
use him standing up over tackle. You can
use him out of a three-point stance. A
guy that's go go go. He's got growth
potential. He's a tall guy who should
get a little bit bigger. Jimmy Rder,
another Michigan guy, a solid offball
linebacker. I I thought he's more fifth
round value, a fifth round pick, but
they need somebody uh they lost. Who's
the kid that went to Tampa Bay that the
Jets wanted? The the blunt analone.
So, they needed somebody to replace him.
Abney, I think he's potentially a good
dime back facing the action. He's a
smaller guy that struggles with his back
to the ball. Kendrick Law, you're
looking at potentially a slot receiver
and return specialist. Skyler Gil Howard
didn't play too much last year because
of an injury, but he's an explosive
undersized one gap tackle.
>> All right, let's go to the Tampa Bay
Buccaneers here, Tony. Um, in the AFC in
the NFC South, um, pardon me. Actually,
I guess I should lead off with the
Carolina Panthers, right? They win that
division on the last game of the year.
So, why don't we go Panthers first here?
I'll I'll try to be accurate with this.
Monroe Freeling, we talked about him.
First round pick 19, developmental um,
left tackle. you understand why they'd
want to do that, but they have Rasheed
Walker. EK Acoin who's going to come
back. Do they move one of those guys
inside? We'll have to see how they
handle that. Auanu specifically when he
returns from injury. Lee Hunter a pick
49. I thought that was the right spot
for him. A run stuffing defensive tackle
they could put next to Derek Brown.
Chris Brazzle in round three, a wide
receiver. I think um another tall guy,
but one with a little bit more speed to
compliment uh Tedo McMillan I think both
of us think that's good value. Will Lee
in round four I think is a good player
picked in the right round. Sam Heck. I
thought he might have been the best
center in this class to be honest with
you, Tony, to get him in round five. I
feel good about that. And then Zaki
Wheatley. I did I did not like him as
much as everyone else. I had kind of
more like a fourth round grade on him. A
lot of people thought he was a day two
guy. He ends up going to them in round
five. So, I thought the Panthers
actually did pretty well here after
Monro Freeling. And we both question the
selection of Monro Freeling. I I think
they did an outstanding job. Lee, you
know, Lee Hunter, he's a guy that's not
going to be relied upon to start as a
rookie. He's very athletic. He's
explosive. He can occupy the gaps as
well as make plays. I thought that was a
terrific pick. I love the selection of
Chris Brazzle. I mean, if they were able
to tap the best out of him along with
Ted McMillan, the size and Brazle brings
the speed. Watch out. That's going to be
a dynamic duo. Will Lee was a great pick
in the fourth round. Some people thought
he should have gone day two. I did not
agree. At the top of his game, Will Lee
is one of the better quarterbacks in
this draft, but he's had injury issues
and he's been up and down. If you can
tap it and get him to play at his
maximum a or his best each each snap,
you've got a player on your hand. I
agree with you about Hec. I thought it
would the Bears would have looked at him
in a day two. Great value in the fifth
round. And Wheatley, I had him as a
sixth round pick. More of a, you know,
between the numbers downhill safety
that'll have to play special teams.
>> All right, let's go over to the Tampa
Bay Buccaneers, Tony. And boy, you could
tell this is a Todd BS draft. just
physical, powerful, heavy-handed type of
players at all at a lot of their spots
here. Ruben Bane Jr., enough said.
Josiah Troder, a super physical inside
linebacker. Ted Hurst, a big physical
wide receiver. Keonte Scott, an
aggressive slot cornerback that is going
to, you know, be a good anticipating for
for picks, but also just a playmaker at
the line. Damonte Kapart around five as
kind of a toolsy defensive tackle
developmental player. I like that. Billy
Shrath, I thought he could have went
earlier than round five. A He has some
injury history, but a physical, mobile,
pretty athletic guard. And then Bower
Sharp, the also big, physical, athletic
tight end out of LSU.
>> I thought they did a great job filling
these with top players. We talked about
Ruben Bane. I thought that was great
value at 15. Josiah Troder, you
mentioned it. And he's he's very much
Todd BS uh type of linebacker. I I mean,
he's great in space. He covers a lot of
area. They lost Levante David. He has
that same sort of style. Ted Hurst, you
know, they lose their uh their top
receiver to in free agency to San
Francisco 49ers. I don't know that Ted
Hurst is going to replace him, but you
know, he he has a buffer there and he's
got a great amount of upside. I thought
Keonte Scott was just great value in the
fourth round. You know, terrific zone
corner or safety. Runs a 4-33 during
proday. I don't know how he got out of
day two. Damonte Kapart. Listen, scouts
have loved him the past three two years,
but he's never come through on a
consistent basis. He's got size, he's
got athleticism, he's got playmaking
ability, but he's very streaky. If
you're able to tap into him and get him
to play up to his level of ability on
every snap, you you got a guy that could
potentially be a starter. Billy Strath,
a good player, made a huge mistake by
not testing uh before the draft. really
did nothing at Proday or combine which
which is what helped which is what
forced him down the draft boards and Bar
Sharp I think could be a very good
number three tight end. All right, let's
go to the Atlanta Falcons here, Tony.
They did not have the first round pick
because of the Pierce trade last year,
but they had Avon Terrell in round
number two, a pick 48. Very good value.
They go with a very small wide receiver,
Zachariah Branch in round three, though,
as a comment to Drake London. All right,
I buy that, right? A speed, shorter
speed, quick guy to comment the bigger
Jake London. I understand that. Uh
Kendall Daniels, linebacker of Oklahoma.
I know a lot of people liked in round
four. And then in round six, Antario
Thompson, a defensive tackle out of
Washington. and they still have a one
more sixth and one more seventh round
pick still to come.
>> I thought they did a terrific job early
on. I mean, Avon Terrell, I think he's
great value at 48. I know a lot of
people, you know, pushed him down
because of the hamstring issue and it
and then he he didn't run well. He he
plays fast. I mean, you never see Avon
Terrell chasing opponents down the
field. He's got terrific playing speed
and he's got real good ball skills. Now
he's paired up with his brother. That
should be fun. Zachariah Branch, as you
said, is a great compliment to Drake
London. more of a gadget player, slot
receiver was red flag from from some
teams because of a knee issue. I guess
the Falcons are are okay with it.
Kendall Daniels, an undersized one gap
explosive type of linebacker, offball
great and space run and chase pursuit
linebacker. Antonio Thompson, a smaller
guy, one gap defensive tackle, three
technique type who doesn't have a lot of
production, but but a player that you're
basically hoping that makes a practice
squad. Could be a player two or three
years down the road.
>> All right, let's go to the next team.
That's the New Orleans Saints. The final
team in the NFC South as we're we're at
a pretty good pace here, Tony. I'm proud
of us so far. We're actually doing this
pretty well. Um Jordan Tyson at pick
number eight. We talked about him a lot.
I love Christian Miller. by the way,
just a lot of traits guys, right? If you
take a look at this group uh for the
Saints, Christian Miller at pick 42, big
athletic. He'll be a great run starter
off the bat. See if he can become more
of a pass rusher as he develops for the
Saints. Oscar Delp, very little
production, but a really good athlete at
pick 73. Maybe a little bit early for my
taste, but if you want a really athletic
tight end, there weren't many of them in
this class that can also block. He can
he has both of those things. Uh, round
four, Jeremiah Wright out of Auburn.
Bryce Lance, I thought was a really good
value pick with their second fourth
round pick. Lorenzo Style, the fifth
round pick. Uh, the very fast
cornerback, Sunny Styles brother out of
Ohio State. He's a safety. And then, uh,
he's a corner. Lorenzo Styles is a
corner, right? Not a safety. Or is he a
safety?
>> I've been told he's going to play
safety, but I think he can also be a
nickel corner.
>> And then Barry and Brown um, would pick
190 in round six. one of again one of
those really small but fast LSU wide
receivers
>> and and very accomplished. I like what
they did after the first round. I mean,
Christian Miller, he's a playmaker. They
need somebody to plug the inside of the
defensive line. He can do it and make
plays behind the line of scrimmage.
Oscar Delp is maybe a projection a year
or two down the road, but if you can
transition that athletic skill into
football production, you have a number
one tight end. And remember, there were
a lot of miles to speed at the in the
Georgia passing game. and he was playing
next to Lucky Lawson who's also going to
be a real good tight end prospect.
Jeremiah Wright, I mean Mickey Lumis
loves his offensive lineman. Jeremiah
Wright is a big powerful power gap type
of lineman who has ability potential
starter two years down the road. Bryce
Lance, I think Bryce Lance was hurt
because he could not perform in the
pre-draft process due to injury. I think
fourth the fourth round is is terrific
value for him. good size, good speed,
good pass catcher, just never got to
show it on a on a bigger scale coming
out of North Dakota State. Lorenzo
Styles, when you I watched him on film
and I had to go back and watch him. He's
more than just a fast guy. He's actually
a very good defensive back. You have to
use him facing the action because he
struggles making plays with his back to
the ball. But I think Styles is going to
be a real good dime either as a safety
or a cornerback and a special teamer.
Barry Brown, I love the receiver. had
some off the- field issues started at
Kentucky. There were some red flags
there, but really he is a terrific pass
catcher who runs precise routes and
separates from defenders and is
relatively effective running after the
catch. I thought that was an outstanding
selection uh by the Saints uh you know
in late rounds. They needed a receiver.
They got three of them who could
actually make their roster this season.
>> Yeah, absolutely right. All right, let's
uh turn our attention to the Los Angeles
Rams. Uh we already Tony talked a lot
about the uh Tai Simpson uh pick at
number 13. Um all the Shawn McVey body
language experts that have been trying
to to figure out what's going on there
afterwards is amusing. Max Claire, I
think you like that pick, Tony, right at
the end of the second round. Um Keegan
Trost, I like that pick. Maybe a little
bit higher than I would have gone, but I
do think he's a really physical athletic
tackle that'll move into guard uh and be
a really effective guard for for the
Rams down the road and maybe even be a
right tackle for them, too. We'll see.
and then uh CJ Daniels in the sixth
round out of Miami. So, not a ton of
picks, which again for the Rams, not a
surprise given how they like to move
their picks around, but
I'm not sure how much this class is
going to help them this year and how
much better they got for 2026.
>> Well, you also have to throw Trent
McDuffy into this class because remember
they had two first round picks and they
used that second first round pick, the
one that was what, the 30th selection to
to trade for Trent McDuffy. So, to be
fair, I agree with you looking at on
paper, but you got to add Trent McDuffy
in here, and he plugged a major hole at
quarterback for the Rams. Uh, we talked
about Ty Simpson, Max Cla, I think he
went where he should have gone. You
know, they like to use a lot of two
tight end sets, so he'll be the move
tight end when they use those two tight
end sets. Keegan Trust, I agree with
you. I have him as a guard. I think he
went earlier than expected. you know,
they're going to have to make they've
got a decision with Warren McClendon to
make after next year. If McClendon plays
well, he's in line for a huge contract,
you know, that they give it to him or
they move forward with Keegan Trust. CJ
Daniels, Devonte Adams is probably in
his last year. CJ, if CJ Daniels shows
anything, I mean, he can make it make
the roster and potentially be that
replacement for Devonte Adams as he's a
bigger, more uh I don't want to say
slower, but he's he's more of a
possession w out with reliable hands.
All right, let's jump over. And this
team should have been first. I told you
I was going to mess up eventually. The
Seattle Seahawks, who won the Super
Bowl. I should have realized that they
were the best team in the NFC West, but
whatever. It's it's late. I'm tired. Um,
just kind of a bunch of solid players
here, Tony. I'm not sure anyone's really
going to, you know, be a huge needle
mover for them, but I suppose Jaren
Price at running back could be. They end
up picking him at the end of the first
round at pick 32. Bud Clark, I like him
as a playmaking safety at the end of
round two. End of round three, they go
Julian Neil, the quarterback out of
Arkansas, a guy with some good size that
you could put out there at outside
corner. Both Stevens in round five, I
think, is right where you're supposed to
be. He has a chance to develop into a a
starting guard in the NFL. And then
Emanuel Henderson Jr. was their first
sixth round pick and they still have one
more six and one more seven to go.
>> I you know, I think for a team that won
the Super Bowl that doesn't have a lot
of holes, I thought this was a
tremendous uh sele draft. We talked
about Jadarian Price. They like to
rotate their backs. That's perfect. and
he's a great pass catcher out of the
back field. Bud Clark was a good player
for three years at the TCU. Had a
tremendous pre-draft process. We saw him
at the Senior Bowl. He was one of the
better defensive backs at the Senior
Bowl. Showed excellent ball skills and
then ran much faster than expected at
the combine. I could see him making the
active roster. Julian Neil is the type
of quarterback that the Seattle Seahawks
love that they just develop. You I find
that they they have that magic touch
touch at the position. Tariq Woolen. We
can go on go back to Sherman. I mean,
he's he's tall, he's big, he's fast, he
just needs to polish the ball ski, his
ball skills and the Seattle Seahawks
find a way to do it. Both Stevens
wouldn't be surprised if he makes the
team because they need another interior
offensive lineman, big tough guy who
gets terrific run blocker, really a
punch in the mouth hit after the whistle
guy. and Emanuel Henderson again, you
know, a taller receiver with good speed
and a lot of people like him as a return
specialist. So, a six- round pick could
eventually make the team make the roster
of a team that won the Super Bowl. I
thought from top to bottom, this was an
outstanding collection of players by the
Seahawks.
>> All right, let's go to the San Francisco
49ers here, Tony. And they traded back a
bunch. Uh it's it's a stockpile. They
end up getting three fourth round picks
out of the deal, but they did not pick
in the first round. They got down to the
first pick in round number two. And
look, I think you're always gonna have
some surprises with the 49ers. You know,
Kyle Shanahan doesn't, you know, give a
you know what, he's just gonna pick the
guys that he likes. Uh Deshan
Stribbling, uh as the first player off
the board in round number two. I
actually really liked him. I thought he
was going to be a good player. I still
thought it was a little bit high given
you probably could have got him a little
bit later if you wanted to. The wide
receiver out of Old Miss, I think
Oklahoma State before that, right if I
recall properly. Um my guy Romelo
Height, they got him at the top of round
three. I like that pick. The edge rusher
out of Texas Tech, older player, but he
has a lot of juice. Kona Ba Black,
pardon me. Surprisingly, he was the
third running back selected end of round
three out of Indiana. I like Grayson
Halton, the defensive tackle out of
Oklahoma in round four. Carver Willis,
the versatile offensive lineman out of
Washington in round four. Ephesians
Pricerback
out of Washington also in round four.
And then one of our favorites, sleepers,
Jaden Duggar, the linebacker out of
Louisiana in round five. And then
Enrique Cruz, the offensive tackle out
of Kansas.
>> Dribbling was moving up draft board. So
when everybody said, "Wow," when they
took him with the 34th pick, I was not
surprised. I mean, because he's big. He
He ran exceptionally well at the
combine. Remember, coming into the
season, he was the highest rated
receiver, uh, senior receiver by NFL
scouts. Just didn't I mean, there were
so many miles to feed at at that
Mississippi offense. Didn't get the
number of targets that he had been
getting at Oklahoma State. I have no
problem with this pick. Romelo height at
definitely the type of sort of
undersized explosive edge rusher that
the San Francisco 49ers like offers
depth and you never know what's going to
happen with Boza after 2026 with his uh
with his contract. I thought Kayen Black
was a bit of a reach. Carver Willis was
a bit of a reach. Ephesians Price was a
bit of a reach. I like Halton. He's you
know an explosive interior one gap type
of lineman. We like Jaden Duger. We saw
him at the Shrine Bowl. He's tall. He's
fast. He's underrated. And Enrique Cruz
was a guy who tested incredibly well at
the combine. He's got great size. He's
more of a developmental type of tackle,
which is really all the ners need at
this point in time.
>> Whether they keep him on the active
roster or try and sneak him on the
practice squad, I thought that was an
excellent fifth round selection.
>> All right, let's go to the Arizona
Cardinals. Jeremiah Love, we talked
about that on on Thursday night's show.
Go check it out. Chase Basantes. That's
a eat your vegetables pick at 034
overall. Like it. They picked the
quarterback Carson Beck at the top of
round three. I guess they didn't want to
take the chance and wait. I thought that
was maybe a little bit rich. He ended up
being the third quarterback off the
board. Uh Caleb Proctor in round four
out of Southeastern Louisiana. There's a
lot of love for him around the league as
one of those small school guys. For me,
round four is a little rich. Uh Reggie
Virgil, the Texas Tech wide receiver in
round five. And then Carson Sherar, the
linebacker out of Iowa in round six.
>> Loved our first two picks. We talked
about love. We talked about him before
the Cardinals even selected him because
we thought it was very likely he was
going to go there. Chase Basantis could
have gone late first round. Went early
second round. He's a move tight end
that's got a great uh great physical
build and terrific upside. I agree with
you about Carson Beck. I I would not
have taken him in day two, but they have
some good offensive minds now in charge
with the Cardinals. So I guess they
think they can turn him around. Agree
with you on Caleb Proctor. An explosive
one gap guy I think would have been uh
available in the sixth round. Reggie
Virgil went where was where he was
expected to go. Tall, shorthanded, not
very fast. Sherara could be a sleeper.
He could be find himself on the waiver
wire. I mean he had one great year of
production at Iowa then tested off the
charts at uh at the combine. He has an
upside, but he's going to have to
produce quickly. Got to in camp this
summer to make the roster. All right,
folks. Don't forget that draft season is
presented by Moody's, a proud partner of
the New York Giants. Decode risk unlock
opportunity. Learn more at moody's.com.
All right, let's jump over Tony to the
AFC East with the Buffalo Bills. We'll
lead off with them. Um, actually, you
know what? I guess I it's still weird. I
don't even think about it this way. We
should lead off with the New England
Patriots. They did make it to the Super
Bowl, so why don't we go there first? I
caught myself that time. Um, Caleb Lomu
with the pick at 28. I I do wonder when
this AJ Brown trade goes down, could he
be redirected? I'm thinking probably
not. Maybe we're looking at a pick next
year instead. Um Gabe Ais, I think, I'd
love that pick in the second round for
the Patriots. I know you probably do,
too. He's a fun player. My guy Eli
Raridan at the end of round three. I
know some people would say too high. I
say no way. He was one of my top tight
ends in the class. Um Karan Prunty in in
round number five, defensive back. I'll
be honest with you, Tony, not that
familiar with him. Please inform me.
Demetrius Crownover, the offensive
tackle out of Texas A&M, gigantic man in
round six. And then Nambdi Obazor out of
TCU, the linebacker also in round six.
>> Well, first of all, the pretty guy from
uh Wake Forest, there's always one or
two players that get drafted that I have
no idea uh on. And he's one of them. SO,
>> WOW. BEAT BEAT BEAT BEAT BEAT BEAT BEAT
BEAT BEAT BEAT BEAT BEAT BEAT BEAT BEAT
BEAT BEAT BEAT T T T T T T T T T T T T T
T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T T
T T T T T T Tony. Wow.
>> You know, well, we'll see. I mean, they
beat me. If he makes the team or makes
the practice quiet, turns out to be a
player, then I looked dopey. If he
doesn't, then you know, I was right.
They should have watched seen the big
follow the big board at essentially
sports. But, you know, Caleb Lemu, he's
a developmental prospect. I I think he's
going to need time before he's NFL
ready. It's an interesting selection
with Will Campbell there. We'll see what
happens. I absolutely agree with you
about Jockis. I thought where they
selected him at the bottom of round two
was great value and he's a terrific
system fit. I also agree with you with
Raridan. He's not super fast, but he's
football fast. He catches the ball
exceptionally well. He's got a long
frame, which can add some bulk, which
would make him a better blocker. Carnov
is a guy that I'm sure that they hope
will start at right tackle in the future
after Morgan Moses hangs up the cleats.
We saw him at the Senior Bowl. I thought
he was really good at the Senior Bowl.
He's got a big frame. He plays big boy
football. uses that massive frame to out
position opponents from the uh from the
ball and and Obi Azor is a terrific
outside terrific offball linebacker.
He's more of a rotational linebacker.
I'm sure they brought him in for special
teams value as well. I thought that was
a nice selection around six.
>> All right, let's jump over uh to the
Buffalo Bills now, Tony. And they moved
around a bunch in this draft.
>> Um you know, Bean was on the phones. He
was moving around. you know, got out of
the first round after a couple move
downs, picked up a bunch of picks. They
end up having three fours and two fives
in this draft. Remember, they traded one
of their mid-round picks for DJ Moore,
but they ended up with two twos, three
fours and two fives, which I think is
pretty good. And I got to be honest with
you, I love what they did with him. Uh
TJ Parker in in round number two, I
think that's great value. Both of us, I
think, thought he could have been an end
of the second half of the first round
type of guy. I'm a big Davidson fan more
than others. I just think his physical
ability, his play style, his aggression,
it's fantastic. The penalties, I know,
but I I do think he is a good football
player. If you can continue to coach
some of that stuff out of him, Jude
Barry in round four, offensive tack out
of BC, that might be a little bit rich
for me there. I thought Skyler Bell in
round four, uh, he's a perfect
compliment or a guy that can kind of do
the same thing Khalil Shakir can if he
gets hurt. Perfect backup to him. Caleb
Elarmms or in the fourth round, one of
your guys, speedy undersized linebacker
out of TCU. I think that's a good pick.
Jaylen Kilgore in round five. I think he
could have been a fourthrounder. That's
good value. The safety slot corner out
of South Carolina. And then Zayn Durant,
another one of the guys that has a lot
of upside. He has to, you know, be more
productive. Smaller defensive tackle,
but he's got some juice in him, some
athleticism. I think round five is a
good developmental bet on him to see if
he could turn him into something. I
really think the Bills did a good job
filling needs and adding depth. I'm
going to disagree with you on Abramos
and I'll tell you why in a second. But
first of all, you start with TJ Parker,
the 35th selection of the draft. I
thought he was worth the first round
pick. I know he didn't have a good year,
but you watch you watch the film. It
wasn't due to lack of effort. He wasn't
mailing it in. He's a perfect fit for
that defense. He's a terrific pass pass
rusher, one gap type of defender that
they like. Igmanosen
if it was three seasons ago after 2023 I
would agree with you. He's been a human
penalty flag since they do like those
bigger you know physical quarterback. So
it's a good system fit. He you know they
just they're just going to put iron
claws on his hands so he can't grab the
opponent and get flagged for pass
interference.
>> He only won four last year. I think he
was a little bit better last year.
He was, but still I I mean Jude Barry,
he's an athletic left tackle prospect
who coming into the season graded out as
a third rounder. Had some injury issues
last year which pushed him down. So you
got to remember that. Skyler Bell, great
receiver, just not a great athlete, not
super fast, runs good routes, catches
the ball extremely well. Elarmms should
have been a day two pick. A tremendous
offball linebacker that fills a
desperate need for the Bills. I thought
Kilgore was a day two pick. You can use
him as a nickel safety. You can use him
as a nickel quarterback. I thought at
times he was much better than Brandon
Cece, his his uh teammate at South
Carolina. Much more polished ball
skills. Remember, he was a terrific
safety in 2024 that South Carolina had
to move to Nickelback out of need last
season and he did a great job. Zayn
Durant's always been one of my
favorites. He's small, he has size
limitations, but he's explosive, he's
athletic, and he plays with a go go go
mentality. I don't be surprised if Zay
Durant not only makes the team, but sees
a lot of playing action as a rookie in
2026.
>> All right, let's jump to the Dolphins
here, Tony. I think we need a full
podcast just to talk about their draft
class. Uh 12 picks. They've made 11 of
them so far. Well, actually, am I
misounting? I'm sorry. 13 picks. They've
made 12 of them so far. Pardon me, I'm
shortch changing the Dolphins. Uh we
talked about Kaden Proctor already at
12. Chris Johnson, my guy at 27, ends up
being the second quarterback off the
board right after
>> um
>> Monsour Delay because McCoy went to the
fourth round. We'll we'll get to him in
a little bit. Um my guy Jacob Rodriguez,
love him at pick 43 in round two.
>> I was a big Caleb Douglas fan, but I was
like, "All right, day three sleeper
round five. Let's go." They pick him at
pick 75 in round three. Will Casmar a
big blocking tight end round four or
five, that's a great pick. Well, round
three at pick 87. Oh, but now we're
cooking again. Chris Bell at pick 94.
All right. Dolphins are a team that can
be patient with him. They're not trying
to really win this year. Good play at
the end of the third round to to try to
develop the player a little bit. Trey
Moore, linebacker out of Texas. Kyle
Lewis in the fourth round. There's great
value to me. Just a good football
player. Michael Taffy, the safety out of
Texas in round five. Kevin Coleman Jr.,
you want a slot receiver that can catch
some passes? Boy, the Dolphins need a
wide receivers and and they they they
got a second one there, but he's going
to catch a lot of balls from this year.
He's just a good solid player. Um, one
of your favorites, Sadu Trayori, the
developmental tight end from overseas uh
in the fifth round. And then DJ
Campbell, the big guard out of Texas in
round number six.
And you know, if if the internet is to
be believed and the board is to be
believed, the Dolphins stole a lot of
these players from teams that that
wanted they stole Kaden Proctor uh from
the Detroit Lions. Evidently, the Jets
were going to take Jacob Jacob
Rodriguez. They took Jacob Jacob
Rodriguez and then the Jets moved back.
Uh Trey Moore, the Cowboys wanted him.
Uh but the the Dolphins I don't Yeah,
they traded up to get Trey Moore. Now,
Chris Johnson, we talked about Crane
Proctor, we talked about Jacob
Rodriguez,
not great in space, not great in
coverage, but the master of the punch
fumble and a guy that, you know, plays,
you know, all out on every single down,
great run defender. Last time the uh
Dolphins had a uh linebacker out of
Texas Tech, guy by the name of Zack
Thomas, who did pretty well. I agree
with you about Caleb Doug Douglas, but
he's big, he's shorthanded, just not a
downfield threat. Casm America is a
blocking tight end who also catches the
ball well. He just didn't have the
opportunity to do that at Ohio State. I
spoke with him about it. He said, "Yeah,
you know, it kind of frustrated him at
time, but don't be times don't be
surprised
>> uh if he gets a lot of balls thrown his
way." Chris Bell, like you said, they're
not they are not building a team to win
in 2026. You give Chris Bell time to get
that knee 100% get back on the field. I
thought third round was a a round later
than he should have gone. Trey Moore,
they have him listed as an edge. Don't
believe that. He is a terrific offball
linebacker. If you watch him play at
UTSA, your Texas San Antonio early in
his career, he showed a lot of ability
as a three down linebacker. Kyle Lewis,
I mean, an explosive one gap linebacker
who, you know, plays much bigger than
his 5'11, 224 foot frame. Michael Taff,
special teamers, smart guy who tested
much better uh than people than he
plays. So, he's got to translate that
speed onto the field. Kevin Coleman, you
mentioned it, slot receiver, catches the
ball well, also brings returnability.
Trayor is the pass catcher that they've
lacked at the receiver position. Uh, and
he's got a tremendous amount of upside.
Campbell, more of a small area guard.
I'll tell you what,
if I'm a veteran on the Miami Dolphins,
I'm very concerned because looking at
this draft, the Dolphins have changed
the face of their team. And don't be
surprised if the majority of these, the
vast majority of these pick, up to 10 of
these selections are on the active
roster come September.
>> And maybe moving some more veterans for
picks in next year's draft as the
Dolphins try to uh put the gas pedal on
the rebuild as they continue to try to
add more people um players in these
drafts. There's a lot of rumors Jordan
Brooks could get traded at some point um
to the Cowboys during or after the
draft. They ended up trading for D
Winters instead. We should have included
that when we did Dallas. They traded one
of their fifth round picks for D
Winters. They need a linebacker help. Uh
so he'll slide in there for them. All
right, let's go to the New York Jets as
we wrap up the AFC East here, Tony. And
we talked about their three first round
picks, but I think both of us thought
they got really good value. David By
two, good player. Kenyan Sadi at 16,
really athletic tight end. Then Omar
Cooper Jr. ended the first round. uh for
me exactly where he should have been. Um
a lot of people thought he would have
been a mid-first round pick, but good
job. They had four other picks uh in
these two and three. D'Angelo Ponds at
pick 50. I think that's about where he
belonged. He's basically Aaron Glenn,
like reborn in like a younger body. So,
I'm not surprised that the Jets liked
him. I thought Daryl Jackson Jr. guy
we've talked a lot about on this show,
the really big Florida State defensive
tackle, top round four, I thought was
good value. Kate Clubnick, developmental
quarterback, that's fine. and I think
long-term backup. And then uh Anus
Cooper, the the big, you know, kind of
bulky road grading guard out of Miami in
round number six. They have one more
seven to go.
>> Like you said, we talked about the trio
first round picks. D'Angelo Ponds could
be a sensational Nickelback. I I I love
this selection, especially where they
got him. You know, as we said, if
D'Angelo Ponds was three, four inches
taller, he's a top 12 pick. He's got
great ball skills. He's very
competitive. He's just limited by his
size. Daryl Jackson was actually a
player I thought the Giants would
consider if they stood around in the
fourth round, but they made that big
trade up to get Malachi Fields. Daryl
Jackson is a tough gap occupier in the
middle of the line. He's also relatively
athletic. He was dominant when we saw
him at the Shrine Bowl, then showed up
for two days of practice at the Senior
Bowl. Not a playmaker, although he seems
to have that playmaking ability. Did
well in the role that they asked him to
play. Kate Clubnick, like you said, you
know, he doesn't have a great arm. He's
a career backup. Which Kate Clubnick are
the Jets getting? Are they getting the
one in 2024 who showed a lot of
development in his game or the guy in
2025 who actually regressed? And Nez
Cooper, you know, people talked about
Maui Goa, but Nez Cooper was was a
terrific offensive guard, a position of
need for the Jets. I uh sixth round I
think is great value, and I think that
this guy's going to make the active
roster once the season opens in
September.
>> All right, let's jump over to the AFC
North, Tony. We'll go with the
Pittsburgh Steelers. famously now they
got Mai Leming kind of plucked from
underneath their hands, but they get
Maxore the the offensive tackle to be a
long-term tackle answer for them. So, I
don't think they should be crying over
that. We talked about him a lot. And
then instead of Mai Lemonard, you get
Jeremy Bernard in round two, a pick 47.
Really nice spot to get him. Really good
shorthanded slot wide receiver. He can
make people miss. Really good player. Uh
Drew Aller in round number three. Mike
McCarthy. Say what you want about him,
Tony. He knows how to develop
quarterback. So, if he can take a year
or two and get all his mechanics and all
that stuff straightened out, maybe he
can turn Drew Aller into something.
We'll see. Dan Everett, a really fast
quarterback out of Georgia in round
three. I think that's a pretty good
pick. Love Jennings dunker in round
three. Road grading guard. I mean, he
just, you know, Pittsburgh Steeler
guard, Jennings dunker just makes sense.
Uh our guy Kaden Witchen uh the the kick
returner, punt returner, slot receiver
um out of Iowa at at pick number 21 in
round four, 121 overall. Um I just like
to see him going off the board. He was
fun to watch at the Shrine Bowl. Then
Riley Noacowski, another very kind of
Mike McCarthy
um Packers fullback. I'm trying to think
of that of of of the White Cowboys uh
fullback that they have. I think he kind
of fills that type of role um where he
gets the ball. The Packers when McCarthy
was there had that same kind of Hback,
fullback, short yardage guy that they
handed the ball off to a lot. I can't
remember that guy's name either, but in
the same category. So, I think that's
how they'll use him. And then Jeremy
Bernard is going to be going to kind of
be like Mike McCarthy's Randle Cobb,
right? And kind of fill that role in
their offense. So, I think the Steelers
did pretty well. Um a lot of players
that I like. We could talk about value
if you want, but I I I do like a lot of
the players that they came out with.
>> I'll take Maxor or the combination of
Maxore and Jeremy Bernard over Mai
Lemon. No doubt about it. I mean,
Bernard is a terrific compliment to DK
Mechaf, a precise route runner who
catches everything. I thought that was a
sensational pick. I'll talk about the
fourth round pick, Wetgen, who you like
you said, terrific pass catcher, a
sensational game impacting return
specialist. you know, he could be their
slot receiver because uh the production
wasn't there at Iowa. I don't know that
he got the opportunities, but when we
saw him in the postseason, no one could
cover him at the Shrine Bowl. Drew, I
mean, we'll see. I I've said all along
Drew Lar needed a change of scenery. I
actually thinks he think he needs to get
out of the state of Pennsylvania, but
he's still there. But you, you know,
you're right about Mike McCarthy. He
knows how to develop quarterbacks. Dylan
Dalen effort I'm not as high on. I mean,
I think he's a better athlete than he is
a defensive back. I think they make a
move to safety because he's got to face
the action. Jennings Dunker along with
Maxore. They got another terrific
offensive line. I had said before the
start of the uh uh the start of day two
on Essentially Sports. Keep an eye where
he's listed, what positions he's he's
listed at, because most teams have him
as a right guard. He was drafted as a
guard. And Noacowsky, as you said, Swiss
Army knife. I mean, a guy who's not
going to be great, but he's going to be
good as a blocker, pass catcher out of
the back field or as a, you know, lining
up in the slot and tight end, also going
to be a good special teamer, and a guy
who came out of nowhere. I mean, he
wasn't even graded by scouts coming into
the season, finds himself as a fifth
round pick.
>> All right, let's go to the Baltimore
Ravens here, Tony. Uh, Yuane, Dingo,
Yuan in round one. We like that. Zion
Young, a pick 45. I think really good
value. I thought he could have been a
pick at the end of the first round. He
was right in that edge run that we had
in in the second round of this draft.
Then two big wide receivers, Jacobe Lane
in round three, maybe a little rich for
me. Elijah Sorado in round four. Like if
you swap those guys, I'm like happy with
the with the round value for me. Uh
Matthew Hibner, the tight end in round
four. Love Chandler Rivers in round
five. I think he's a walk-in starting
slot if they want to play him there. Uh
Josh Quas, the tight end of Alabama,
good receiver in round five. Adam
Randall, the big bruising running back.
also on round five and then Ryan Eckley
the punter out of Michigan State in
round six and they still have two more
seventh rounders to go.
>> One of my favorite drafts. I I mean
Ionian is gonna be a day one starter.
Wouldn't surprise me if Zion Young's a
day one starter. I mean a terrific edge
rusher who also plays the run well. He's
very athletic. He's tall. He's just got
to put some meat on his bones. I mean
he's a little bit thin but he's got
great upside. I agree with you about
Jacobe Lane and Elijah Serat but the
fact is this. I think it complements
what they have on their roster at the
position. Safe Flowers very very well.
You got two bigger body possession wide
outs. Lane's a little bit thin, but
still he he's got good length and can
add some uh some weight to his body. I
thought Matthew Hner, it's a good
potentially good replacement for Isaiah
likely. I mean, he's faster than Likely
as far as 40 times concerned. A terrific
pass catcher. And then they come back
with Quava who's also a real good pass
catcher and blocker. and Ekley. You
never know. Eckley could make the team.
Could be a starter uh this this season.
I thought overall this is one of my one
of my favorite drafts from top to
bottom.
>> Hey, look. And I like the Bengals draft
too, Tony. Let's jump there. Dexter
Lawrence is their first round pick in
that trade for 10th overall. Cashes
Howell a pick 41 with the juice he has
off the edge. They need an edge rusher.
I think that's a good selection. I like
to Takario Davis more than other people.
I think a pick 72 that's good value for
him. Connor Louu in round four coming
off that ACL. They'll have to see where
he's at. Maybe a little rich for me. Uh
Kobe Young in round four, the big wide
receiver out of Georgia. Brian Parker, I
thought great value in in round number
six. I actually like him better than
Connor Lou to be totally honest with
you. So I love the value there. And then
Jack injuries in round seven. Tony,
look, I'll be honest with you. Like
looking at these guys and and when you I
went through this tight end, I had
trouble separating them. Like am I sure
that Max Cla is definitely a better
player than Jack in? I don't know. To
me, they were pretty close to be totally
honest with you. So, to get injuries in
round seven, I feel pretty good about
that.
>> The thing thing about it is is Claire
was incredibly productive in 2024. His
production took a step back last year at
Ohio State and you know, you would know
why because they have such great
receivers and had a good running game. I
thought Endries really uh did a
disservice to himself by entering the
draft. I thought he was a good tight end
that needed another year on the college
level. Uh Cashes Howell I thought was
great value the top of round two. I I
mean he's uh they to they took Shamar
Stewart last year in the first round.
Basically, he will be able to kick
Shamar Stewart in the rear end and give
him a good kick start because that's the
way he plays. People talk about the
short arms. I'm not worried about that.
Yeah, I know you need him to keep the
blockers off you, but he finds ways to
make plays. Takario Davis, I I mean, I
like him, but I don't I would have I
thought he was more of a day three type
of guy. He's got great upside. He was
terrific at Arizona. At one point during
early in his college career at Arizona,
people thought he was going to be a
first round pick. His play has kind of
fallen off. We'll see if they were able
to uh uh to uh to develop him. Connor
Lou and Brian Parker. It's interesting.
Obviously, one guy's going to play
guard. It could be Parker who was the
right tackle at Duke and Lou. You don't
know when he's going to be coming back
from that knee surgery, but offensive
line has been a problem for the uh
Bengals. They get two good ones. I
thought Kobe Young good receiver but he
was taking about two to three rounds
earlier than I should than I thought he
should have been. Much quickness or
speed catches the ball well possession
wide out that's also a red zone threat.
>> All right Tony let's kick over to the
since the Cleveland Browns the final
team in the AFC North. Uh Spencer Fat
and Casey Cepio the two first round
picks they want an offensive lineman and
a wide receiver. I think we're both uh
pretty impressed with that they got both
those guys. Then they double down on
wide receiver and Denzel Boston goes uh
in round number two. Tony, I love that
pick. I both first round grades or late
first round grades on Conception and
Boston. So I think that's a good
combination. Love Emanuel McNeel Warren.
I think that's kind of where you thought
he should have been picked, Tony, right?
Instead of being a firstrounder.
>> And then I'll be honest with you, the
rest of these picks not as inspiring for
me. I thought they did great early.
Austin Barber at around three was early
for me. I see him as more of a guard
than a tackle. Parker Brazford in round
five with Justin Jefferson who I really
think is just a special teams player. Uh
Joy Royer the tight end out of
Cincinnati. I think he's a sixth or
seventh rounder. And then Taywin Green
the kind of toolsy quarterback out of
Arkansas. We'll see if they keep him at
quarterback or they try to move in the
tight end or something like that. So I
thought a really good start at the top
for the Browns. Not as excited about the
the back end.
>> I you know I I like this draft from
start to finish. Maybe Parker
Braillesford, not as much because he's a
smaller guy. But, you know, Denzel
Boston is the perfect compliment to
Casey Conpsion. Casey Conception, the
first round pick, take the top off the
defense. He's speedy. He's a terrific
pass uh return specialist. Denzel
Boston, the bigger possession wide out.
So, I thought that was a great
compliment. You said you hit the nail on
the head as far as I'm concerned with
Emanuel McNeel. I'm not a big fan of
his, but I think the 58th pick was good
value and they needed help in that
secondary. I like Austin Barber. I like
his upside. The fact is, you know, they
need a lot of help on that offensive
line. So, they drafted their, you know,
they took a college right tackle who
they project to the left side and
Spencer Feno and now they take a college
right left tackle who maybe they project
to the right side. You say guard. We'll
see. Uh Parker Brailford, good uh
center, but he's got size limitations.
Justin Jefferson, I I like Jefferson. I
I think he's underrated. small, doesn't
have great size, but a terrific offball
linebacker who can play special teams.
Joe Royer is going to be a perfect
compliment to Howard Fannon. Howard
Fannon, your move down the field tight
end, who's a terrific pass catcher.
Royer's much bigger, terrific blocker
and a short to intermediate pass
catcher. And why not roll the dice on
Taylor Green? I mean, if you can coach
him and you can develop him, you going
to have some you could have potentially
somebody special at the quarterback
position. Now, that's a big ask, but why
not? I like this draft, as is usually
the case with the Cleveland Browns. The
problem is taking what looks good on
paper and turning it into production on
the field, but I'm sure Brown fans have
got to be happy with what they've seen
the past three days.
>> I love the first four picks, Tony. I
think that that might be the best first
four besides the teams that maybe had
three ones or something like that. Uh
that that might be the best four pick
first four picks, I think, for any team
in the draft. I thought they did really,
really, really well. All right, let's
jump. Go ahead. I thought you were going
to say something.
>> No.
>> Oh, sorry. All right, let's go down to
the AFC South now. We'll lead off with
the Jacksonville Jaguars. Interesting
draft. Uh Nate Boracher at the end of
the second round. I like Boricature more
than most, but I thought he was more of
a day three guy. Albert Regis, the big
defensive tackle of Texas A&M in round
three. Uh my favorite player from their
draft class was their third player pick,
Emanuel Pregnon. Uh they got him a pick
88. I thought excellent value for him.
Uh Jaylen Husky, the safety out of
Maryland in round three. Wesley
Williams, a guy we liked at the Shrine
Bowl, was kind of a a twitchy underside
edge player. Tanner Kosil in round five.
And then Josh Cameron, the kind of
really weird like 200 like where's 44?
He's like a 230 lb like short wide
receiver. Um he got picked in round six.
And so three more picks to go for them.
>> I I mean the first two picks kind of
surprised me if not dumbfounded me. B
Kercher. I I mean, yeah, I I is he he's
got some nice traits, but to me, he's a
day three pick and he's nothing better
than a number two tight end at the next
level. I don't think he's going to be a
starter. He's not really big. He's not
really fast. Gets the most from his
ability, but still late second round.
Regis is more of a one gap, 61 and a
half, 288 pound type of defensive
lineman. Don't seem great upside in him.
I love the third round pick and Emanuel
Pregnant. Why did he fall? Well, number
one, the people from USC told me that he
was a little bit difficult to deal with
when he was at USC. And then his own
team said, you know, the word was he
he's going to struggle to mentally
absorb offensive systems. Doesn't
matter. Home run hit here with for the
uh for the Jaguars in the third round.
This guy's got starting potential.
Jaylen Husky in the third round was a
little bit early for me, but he is a
real good player. We saw him at the
Shrine Bowl. Tested incredibly well at
the combine. He's got good film. Wesley
Williams again a little bit early in the
fourth round for me but he is he is a
smaller explosive edge rusher. I like
Tanner Kosil better in the fifth round
than I do Kercher in the second round.
Kosil is a terrific pass catcher.
Incredibly productive at Ball State two
seasons ago. Production dropped off last
year at Houston, but he's got an upside.
And Josh Cameron I thought was
ridiculously underrated. You know he's
built more like an Hback, a little
shorter, wider pass catcher. doesn't
have great speed, but he catches the
ball incredibly well, and he came away
with a lot of important receptions the
past two years at Balor.
>> Okay, let's go to um who's up next here?
I already have the team up. Uh Houston
Texans. Um this is a All right, we're
going to become bigger, more physical,
and we're going to just try to kick your
butt type of draft, Tony. And I'm I'm
here for it. Kaylin Rutled at pick 26.
You've talked about him maybe a little
rich, but look, he certainly they needed
a guard and you could argue he's the
best guard in the class after Yuan. Uh
Katie McDonald, big powerful runs
stopping defensive tackle to add to
what's already an impressive defensive
front. Marlon Klene, he's he's an upside
swing. End of round two I think is a
little bit rich for me, but man, he can
run block. Um, Fabeti Nawahu, I think in
round four, a center or guard, depending
on where you want to play him, but I
think a solid player, even if maybe the
upside's not super high. Your guy Wade
Woodazz in round four, you've been
pumping him up all year on draft season,
Tony, gets into the fourth round. Good
for him. Kamari Ramsey out of USC, kind
of that safety slot corner type in round
five. And then Lewis Bond, wide receiver
out of Boston College. I think it was
the Senior Bowl where we saw him, Tony,
where he was actually pretty effective
as a slot wide receiver. Well, he was a
terrific receiver at Boston College and
he was one of the bigger uh combine
snubs. Now, the problem with Lewis Bond
is he's got average size. He's under six
foot tall, about 190 pounds, and then he
runs in the high four or fives uh during
proday, so he's not fast, but he is an
outstanding receiver. He gets he
>> should have been invited and he catches
the ball incredibly. He's also smart,
like you said. He gets open. So, I I
mean, they need a receiver. Bond can
absolutely make the roster uh as a
number as a four a fifth receiver on
that squad. Keelin Rutled had been uh
rising up draft boards if you read my
stuff at essentially sports. No surprise
he went uh late first round. Kade
McDonald they moved up in front of the
Giants to make sure they get Kade
McDonald a bigbodied uh nose tackle that
they need. And I talked to some people
and they I was surprised that they agree
with me because a lot of people usually
don't. But, you know, he's been he he's
been kind of miscast as just a gap
occupier, not a playmaker. And people
see playmaking ability in Cade McDonald,
which I thought all along. He just
wasn't asked to use to do it at Ohio
State because they didn't need him to do
it because they had those guys on the
edges in Kenyatta Jackson will be a
first round pick next year. Kaden Curry,
who's going to be a PFA this year, and
Taiwan Malone, a smaller one gap guy.
So, I was glad to hear that. Completely
agree with you, Marlon Klein. I I mean
this is a guy you're drafting for two or
three years down the road. I think he
had 24 receptions last year. Size speed
guy with limited physical uh with
limited football production. The
Oklahoma interior lineman. Completely
agree with you. Wouldn't be surprised
after taking Keelin Rutled in the first
round. They try and move him into center
because they need a center. Wade with I
mean I love this pick. I I thought this
guy did not have a good year. Was
injured like a lot of the Clemson
players. Did not live up to
expectations. You watch the 2024 film.
He was a tremendous instinctive
linebacker. He tested incredibly well at
the combine. Just a matter of him
pulling it all together. Kamari Ramsey,
I thought he he basically did himself a
disservice. Uh should have gone back to
school for another year, which is why he
ended up in the fifth round. All right,
let's wrap up the AFC South Tony. The
Tennessee Titans, they move up at the
end of round one and at the end of round
two. That cost them their third and
fourth round picks um in this draft, but
they come away with some players.
Carlton and Kendrick Faulk. We talked
about that already. Um whether the order
of that was right. Anthony Hill I
thought is good value of pick 60 in
round number two. I like that selection.
And then we're looking at fifth, sixth,
and seventh round picks here. Fernando
Carmona, uh the guard out of Arkansas in
round five with Nicholas Singleton. I
thought that is a a good swing for an
athletic running back. Uh Jackie
Marshall, defensive tackle out of Balor
in round six with Pat Kugan, the Indiana
center. And then Jiren Canick, uh, the
tight end of Oklahoma, out of Oklahoma
in round number seven.
New regime, Tony. I think they got some
good players. I'm not sure they maximize
the value of their picks, though.
>> Yeah, I completely agree with you. I
mean, does Anthony Hill make up for
passing Sunny Styles with the fourth
pick of the draft? I I don't know.
Orville.
>> Anthony Hill.
>> Yeah. Well, or Reese, but I think
Anthony Hill compares more to Sunny
Styles. That's fair. sort of that speedy
one gap linebacker that uh well Sunonny
Styles not one gap linebacker but but
that sort of type of player that Robert
Solo likes. Nick Singleton I think could
be really good value uh in the fifth
round if he gets back to where he was in
2024 because he did not have a good
season last year. Carmona I had him as a
free agent. I mean he's a he's a tough
small area blocker. Any dis he he
struggles any distance off the line of
scrimmage. He struggles any uh movement
to his left or his right. I I think that
was a bit of a reach. Jackie Marshall,
more of your one gap type of explosive
lineman. He may struggle and make the
roster. Pat Hugan can play guard or
center. The type of guy you want on your
roster as he gets the most from his
ability. He plays hard every down and
he's very tough. Kik came out of nowhere
from uh from Oklahoma this year. Sort of
an undersized tight end that I think
will be headed for the practice squad.
All right, let's jump over to the AFC
West. Tony, the Denver Broncos. Shawn
Payne likes to trade picks. Uh, so
that's that's what he does. So, right
now only four players. They have three
more seven round picks to go as as the
draft continues. Tyler Onetum in round
number three um out of Texas A&M the
three technique. Jonah Coleman around
four. I think he could maybe break into
that running back rotation with the guys
they have. All right, he could comment
RJ Harvey I think pretty well uh as the
in between the tackles guy versus the
Harvey explosive guy. uh Cage Casey, the
offensive tackle out of Boise State.
Maybe he converts into guard. We'll see.
But I do like the Justin Jolie pick in
round number five. I think, you know,
Shawn Payne's always looking for that
passcatching tight end. And I think he
will at least fill that role um along
with Evan Ingram for the Broncos this
year.
>> Absolutely has the ability to needs to
step it up and play at a consistently
high level on every single down. I I
mean, he's a relatively athletic guy.
He's an agile pass catcher. He just
disappears for long streaks. Onium, they
lost John Frank John Franklin Meyers in
in free agency. He's a good replacement
for him. Same sort of style and st
substance to this game. Joel Nicoleman,
I thought there were better running
backs on the board, but the way the
running backs fell off the board this
year was very weird because not a lot of
them were drafted and a lot of the guys
we thought would go early fell into the
fifth round, but still good as a
rotation. Cage Casey I think will be a
sort of a a backup guard tackle may
eventually develop into a a starting
right guard. I already mentioned Justin
Jolly and remember I mean they used
their first round pick on Jaylen Wadd.
Uh so you have to factor that into this
draft.
>> All right let's jump over to the Los
Angeles Chargers here. Tony Keem Mesador
pick 22. Again check out Thursday's show
if you want to find out our thoughts on
all these first round picks. Um Jake
Slaughter at the end of round two. that
to me was a little bit rich. He's more
of a round four type of guy for me. Um
but I know other people really thought
he was he was a really good player. He
was at the Senior Bowl. Um Brennan
Thompson, the speedster wide receiver in
round four. Two other fourth round picks
kind of in my opinion developmental left
tackle, really tall. Travis Burke out of
Memphis. Jenis Smith, the ball hawking
safety out of Arizona also in round
four. I like those those two picks,
those three picks really as guys you can
develop with some traits that you can
work with. Um Nick Barrett in round
five, the defensive tack out of South
Carolina. And then Logan Taylor and Alex
Harky, two guards in round number six. I
mean, I think Messador is the only guy
that's really going to step in in year
one and and really impact from this
class. Tony,
>> and even that, he doesn't have much
upside because he's an older prospect. A
very uninspired draft as far as I'm
concerned. I was never very big on Jake
Slaughter. I mean, he's not a big power
gap guy. He's not an overly athletic uh
uh motion guy. I know that teams like
the Houston Texans like them in day two.
We'll see if I'm wrong. Although Brennan
Thompson was a good pick in the fourth
round. He's a good pass catcher. Ran the
426 at the combine. He's just a smaller
guy. Travis Burke I thought was is a
good developmental prospect. You could
have got him in the seventh round.
Genesis Smith, one of my personal
favorites, although he's got scheme
limitations. Nick Barrett, I thought
would have been available later on in
the draft. Logan Taylor, a good swing
lineman, can play guarder tackle. Alex
Harky very serviceable. There's just
nothing to get excited about uh with
this draft with this group of players as
far as I'm concerned. The Chiefs the
opposite. I think they had some fun
picks. Tony Monsour Delane at picked
number six in the tradeup. Peter Woods
at pick 29. Say what you want. He
certainly has the athletic upside to
become a really good player. Arason
Thomas at pick 40. I thought that was
about right where he should be. you
know, maybe he's a little bit lower on
my board, but I think if you're looking
for a speed guy that's going to
challenge the edge, I think that's a
fine pick there at 40. No third round
pick for the Chiefs. Uh I believe they
use that to in their move up from 9 to
six if I'm not mistaken. Right. Uh Jaden
Kennedy, the quarterback out of Oregon
around four. I loved Emtt Johnson around
five. I thought that was extremely good
value. Um if if you play fantasy
football and you have Kenneth Walker,
draft Emma Johnson. He will be the guy
if Walker gets hurt, which he has in the
past. Cyrus Allen, the wide receiver out
of Cincinnati in round five and then
they have a one more pick in round seven
pending here. This is except for Monsour
Delane. In my opinion, this is a hit or
miss draft. I mean, Peter Woods, which
Peter Woods is going to show up this
September, the guy from 2024 or the guy
who was invisible in 2025? Arm Mason
Thomas, he fits the mold that they like,
but and he plays hard. He's a hustle
guy, but he doesn't have great size. I
think he's going to struggle against
some of the bigger tackles. I'm sorry I
never saw it with Jaden Kennedy and I
watched him time and time again. I know
that scouts loved him. Maybe I'm wrong.
I would agree with you about EMTT
Johnson. He's a good situational runner.
He's got to run learn to run a little
bit lower and behind his pads. Gets a
little bit too upright for me. The only
thing I don't like about Johnson is he's
205 pounds and he runs like a power run
on the inside. But as a situational ball
carrier, I like him. And the Chiefs have
had good success with late round running
backs like uh Isaiah Pacheco where their
early round running backs have turned
into a bus.
>> Johnson's also a good receiver by the
way. He can catch the ball well.
>> Cyrus Allen uh very good. I mean he's
not super big. He's not super fast, but
he catches the ball extremely well. Had
a very productive season last last year
at Cincinnati. Uh could be a good number
five receiver on Sunday.
>> Really cool scene, by the way, in round
seven of the draft as we wrap up this
thing. And we still got a bunch of picks
to go. But our guy, Eli Hidenrike, out
of Navy, who we had a chance to talk to
at the Shrine Bowl, really nice kid,
gets picked by the Steelers, comes out
in full Navy uniform. I love it. Waving
the terrible towel going to Pittsburgh.
Mike McCarthy,
>> you know, good good on him for going to
the draft because he knew he knew he was
going to be a day three pick. And the
fact that the Steelers to I mean Rocky
Blar for those of us who remember Rocky
Blar with the Steelers. I mean that
that's got to be fantastic.
>> Mike McCarthy loves these like backfield
slot guys that you can throw the ball
to. They drafted like three of them this
year now. So I think we'll see how they
decide to use all these guys. But I just
like seeing the guys from the
servicemies get drafted. So Eli
Hidenrike uh off the board uh to the
Pittsburgh Steelers as I kind of get
distracted here. Um, our final team,
Tony, um, the Las Vegas Raiders, who had
the first overall pick. I guess it makes
sense that they're the final team that
we do here. They moved around the draft
a lot, too. Picking up picks back and
forth. Um, I'm kind of excited about
what I saw here to be honest with you.
Um, maybe not the best value at some
spots, but I do like the set of players
that they walked away with. Um, when you
look at the names, Fernando Mendoza,
obviously first overall, can't complain.
I thought Trade Stooks at 38 was a
little bit rich. I'm not surprised. I
heard he was jumping up draft boards. Uh
but a good a good kind of tone setter on
defense. Kind of a slot corner safety
type. Uh Kron Crawford right at the end
of uh beginning of round three. Maybe a
little rich for me, but he's got some
speed off the edge if you want a guy
that can rush the passer. Uh Trey Zoo, I
think you could argue he was the best
center in this class. I know I mentioned
that for Sam Heck. I think Zoo was in
that conversation as well. Uh converted
tackle. Maybe they can use McGuard. I
don't know how they're going to use him.
Um, at the end of round three, then
Jamal McCoy at the top of round four.
Why not at that point? Roll the dice. He
could end up being the best position
player in that class if his knee holds
up. Um, after uh Fernando Mendoza, Mike
Washington around four to back up uh
Genty. I think that's a good value pick.
Then Dalton Johnson, Hezekiah Masses,
Malik Benson, the speedster wide
receiver out of Oregon, and Brandon
Cleveland, the defensive tackle out of
NC State. Overall 10 players here
drafted for the Las Vegas Raiders. Tony
>> Trayon Stokes could have ended up in the
bottom part of round one. I mean, he's
an explosive defensive back that you can
line up at safety or corner or nickel.
He's got great size, ran 433 at the
combine, a guy that was rising up
boards. He's got a high upside. Keon
Crawford, not the biggest guy in the
world, but a terrific pass rusher that
goes very hard on every single down. You
mentioned Trey Zoom. He projects to
center, although he had did play center
some last year at Texas A&M and then we
saw him at center uh during the Senior
Bowl, so it may take a little bit of
time there. I I tend to agree with you
about Jamad McCoy. We'll see what
happens with him. I mean, I I was told
before the day two, there's a chance he
may have to retire. He's going to very
likely have to undergo another procedure
uh with something that's called a bone
plug. If it doesn't hold, he may no
longer be able to play football, but in
the fourth round with that upside pro,
he's probably not going to. It's very
unlikely he's going to play in 2026
because he's he's going to need another
procedure, which is why he fell. But why
not with all these picks, you know, it's
a fourth round choice. Big deal. Mike
Washington, completely agree with you.
Great compliment to Ashton Genty, who's
a terrific perimeter ball carrier.
Washington is a grinder and a pounder on
the inside with great speed. surprised
he lasted this long. Dalton Johnson a
bigger strong safety type uh masses the
the corner from safety. Another big body
guy I think is good in zone. Malik
Benson sort of sort of a slot receiver
return specialist. Brandon Cleveland's a
guy that's got great tools yet never put
it together on a consistent basis at
North Carolina State. He's either going
to be on the active roster practice
squad or he's going to get cut. He's
going to have to come into camp this
summer and really kick it into gear
immediately in order to have a chance.
>> Tony, that's the 2026 NFL draft. Do you
want to give me your favorite class? Do
you have one off the top of your head? I
don't mean to put you on the spot here,
but do you have one class that really
jumped out to you that was better than
all the rest? I
>> I like what most of the teams in the AFC
North did. I like what Pittsburgh did. I
like what Baltimore did. I like what
Cleveland did. I I mean, the Steelers
needed offensive linemen and receivers.
They got both. Uh Baltimore needed
players on both sides of the lines of
scrimmage. They did that and they got
receivers. They got reliable receivers
like in the past where they've they've
missed on so many receivers. And the
Browns, you know, we've talked about I
think they they did well at the top and
I think they got some good complimentary
players later on. How about yourself?
Yeah, you know, I don't know if I have a
favorite. I'll just talk locally. I I I
thought the Giants had a really nice
draft, Tony, to be honest with you.
>> Um I I think to get Avo Arll Ree at at
at pick number five overall, you know, I
can't give them too much credit. I guess
he fell in their laps, but good for them
for taking him. Um I thought it was a
pretty easy decision, but man, you know,
teams screw it up all the time. So,
really good job by the Giants taking
Arbor Reese there. Co hood in round two
I think is a really good pick. You
always want to help your young
quarterback. The Giants needed to
reinforce that interior offensive line
not just for this year but even more
importantly for the future where they
don't have a ton of players on their
contract at that position. So I think
that was a really good move for them.
And and then Malachi Fields in the
tradeup. Look we saw day three Tony
these draft boards all over the place
right? Y
>> like
day three look at some of those picks
starting you know the beginning of the
third round. I mean some of those guys
that went in the third round you know
were projected consensus wise as late
round picks.
>> Yeah. Jake Slaughter was a picked at the
end of the second round. Nate Borcature,
right? Like these are guys that we
thought were round five or six guys.
>> Jay Jaylen Husky.
>> Exactly. Right. So, if you want to use,
you know, I I I don't love trading from
next year's draft, but if that was the
price, I don't care. Move up. Get a good
player like Malachi Fields. I think you
feel good about it. He's he's a good uh
different type of piece to your point to
put in that wide receiver group across
from Malik Neighbors and Darnell Movie
and Calvin Austin and and then Darius
Sllayton as a bigbodied wide receiver
that Jackson Dart um can throw to. He's
got a Raptor um type of wingspan. So, I
I just think the Giants did really well
with the picks that they had. I like the
fact that they were aggressive uh to go
up and get fields. they might get that
draft pick back next year uh in maybe a
comp pick if Kayon Tibido leaves in free
agency at some point down the road or if
um there's a trade they get a comp pick
for Wanda Robbins. So I was just happy
with what the Giants did. I think you
got to be happy. They fill needs while
at the same time getting value picks for
those needs. So I thought they did a
nice job.
>> Well, you know, and people are talking
about don't trade picks for 2027. Those
are the teams that need quarterbacks
because you want to accumulate draft
assets in case you want to move up to
get one of the quarterbacks.
>> Yeah. Giants don't have to worry about
that. They have their quarterback.
>> All right. My voice is about to to to to
die in me, Tony. So, I'm I'm happy we're
done. Um, we'll be back on WFN tomorrow,
by the way, for fans that are local or
just go to the Odyssey app. You can
stream the show. Um, we're going to be
on from 11 to 1:30. Tony and I will
figure out when he's going to be on as
soon as we say goodbye here. But he'll
call in at some point during that show
with me, Paul Dino, and Mark Malus. And
uh, we'll talk to you then. Until then,
that's all the time we have for draft
season. Brought to you by Moody's, a
proud partner of the New York Football
Giants. Uniting the brightest minds to
turn today's risks into tomorrow's
opportunity. Farewell from the Giants
podcast studio. By the learn more at
moody's.com. Farewell from the Giants
podcast studio presented by Hacken Sack
Health. Keep getting better. For Tony
Pauline, I am John Schmuck. We'll have
one more draft season this year uh
detailing the look ahead to the 2027
draft class. We'll probably record that
the end of this week, post it at the
beginning of next week. I think is a
good laudable goal here. Let everyone
absorb this draft class this year and
then we can look next week into the
class next year. But Tony, give me some
names so I can watch some tape this week
because I I'm just going to find random
list online and start watching dudes um
to to at least try to bring some
knowledge to this discussion before my
summer scouting starts for the 2027
class. Anything on Essentially Sports
that you have coming out that you want
fans to keep an eye on? Well, we we'll
have a review of of the draft. We'll
have a review review a review draft
show. You can watch our live streams
from day one and day two. They were act
I actually enjoyed them. There's a lot
of information there. We had a lot of
guests. It was a lot of fun as well.
>> All right, good stuff. Check that out,
folks. Thanks for being with us. And
take Sunday off. Don't think about
football. Reintroduce yourself to your
families. Go out
>> Well, it's supposed to rain tomorrow in
the tri-state airs. I'm not sure that's
happening.
>> Sweep the sweep the garage. touch some
wet grass and enjoy yourself away from
the television and um go Knicks tonight.
Don't don't don't put me in a bad mood
for the rest of the weekend. Please,
just just get the series to 22, please.
I'm I'm I'm absolutely begging you for
Tony Pauline. I'm John Schmelk. We'll
see you next week.